And not only because I got my dream car,
but this morning on S C K T.
I caught a 230% squeeze unless then
five seconds now. As always,
I'll be saving the most explosive stock for last,
so make sure to watch the full video.
Let's go ahead and dive right into it. Now.
First up on the list
we have the one that I caught this morning on the stream again.
230% in five seconds. So it only makes sense to watch it again tomorrow.
S C K T. I wanna watch this.
If price show strength over $2 and 50
then from there this looks awesome.
Awesome pullbacks
even puts some place a nice higher low bottom over VWAP and over 2 20. Again
pullback opportunities for the next leg higher
back to 4 and 5 bucks to share.
Next we have the massive Chinese gap here in after hours
and Chinese stocks been crazy hot.
So this thing should be on your list for tomorrow too.
That is W A F U.
Now the game plan here is gonna be just to watch for strength in the morning
somewhere over VWAP,
over 2 ten and if it shows strength in the morning to confirm a day 2 move.
This looks fantastic. If It does.
We have range back to three,
four and five bucks a share.
Then number three, last and certainly not least,
the most explosive stock for Tuesday's trading.
They actually caught this this morning.
A massive play. 30%.
And it looks crazy for a day two move.
Now, before I give you my entire game plan,
I give you the top three stocks in the market every single night
for completely free. So please do me a massive favour.
Hit that like button to say thank you.
Hit the follow button too.
So you're tuned in every single night for my top stock watch list
just like this. Now that stock here is M T E N.
I had a 30% win on this this morning in the live stream.
And I wanna watch it again tomorrow.
If we find strength over today's high of day
for one dollar and seventy eight cents.
If price does find strength over those highs over 1 78.
Pullbacks here look awesome again.
Back over. View up.
Back over 1 60. Put in place a nice high,
low bottom. Then we have range back to the upside again.
Two, three,
four and five bucks a share.
This thing has a lot of room.
Now, of course,
to get my entire watch list every night,
every morning. To watch me trade these stocks and so many others.
Just like this morning in S C K T.
It was crazy. And to use my stock Scanner trading journal,
education, chat room access and everything else.
Make sure to go lock in your seven day free trial.
Important announcement to come for members here. Uh,
this week you might be getting something.
Well, you'll see.
I'll tell you later this week.
And of course, let me know in the comments below
which one of these three stocks is your favourite for tomorrow.
And that being said, I better see you in the stream in the morning.
And that's seven day free trial. I'll see you there.